<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

						<!--======= Cannery =======-->

						<ThingDef ParentName="BuildingBase">
							<defName>VFEM_ProvisionsPackagingFactory_Cannery</defName>
							<label>cannery</label>
							<description>A medium-sized factory module that accepts raw food before vaccuum packing and sealing it tightly, allowing it to last indefinitely. Does not require additional steel after creation.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733&gt;Automation Chain:&lt;/color&gt; Part of the Provisions Packaging Factory (P.P.F.) chain.</description>
						</ThingDef>												

						<!--======= Industrial Cheese Press =======-->

						<ThingDef ParentName="BuildingBase">
							<defName>VFEM_IndustrialCheesePress</defName>
							<label>industrial cheese press</label>
							<description>A tank capable of rapidly heating milk until curds begin to form, then automatically strains and presses them into multiple wheels of cheese at once. Nearby hoppers can hold enough milk to make several wheels and finished wheels will automatically be dispensed. Quality cheeses can be forcibly aged more quickly than powerless aging methods.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733&gt;Automation Chain:&lt;/color&gt; The Industrial Cheese Press is not part of any automation chain, it is an independent building.</description>
						</ThingDef>
						<!--======= Industrial Soup Vat =======-->

						<ThingDef ParentName="BuildingBase">
							<defName>VFEM_IndustrialSoupVat</defName>
							<label>industrial soup vat</label>
							<description>A very large vat with a series of mounted, spinning blades towards the top. Attached hoppers can be filled with a variety of raw food products. Thereafter they are vacuumed through the top, sliced and simmered deeply into a variety of soups. Finished soups will be dispensed to an opposing hopper without the need of processing steps. Input and output both are done en masse and require much less management than traditional slow cooking.\n\nGourmet soups are obviously not created industrially.\n\n&lt;color=#33d733&gt;Automation Chain:&lt;/color&gt; The Industrial Soup Vat is not part of any automation chain, it is an independent building.</description>
						</ThingDef>